<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">IARUnlocks</string>
    <string name="version" translatable="false">2025.08.0</string>
    <string name="app_name_translatable" translatable="true">I am rich</string>
    <string name="info_button">Info</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="source_code_button">Source Code</string>
    <string name="website_button">Website</string>

    <!--  URL  -->
    <string name="source_code_url" translatable="false">https://github.com/Perkedel/I_am_rich</string>
    <string name="website_url" translatable="false">https://perkedel.netlify.app</string>

    <!--  Manifesto  -->
    <string name="iar_manifesto">I am rich\nI am very health \u0026 successful\nI deserve it\nI am glad</string>
    <string name="iar_congratulations">Thank you for your purchase. You have unlocked all premium features for <b>ALL OF PERKEDEL apps</b>. Congratulations!\nPlease keep this software installed to keep your premium features</string>
    <string name="iar_disclaimer">Disklaimer:</string>
    <string name="iar_disclaimer_long">This piece of software was made for the purpose of parody. Any resemblance of software products: real, fake, or defunct; are purely coincidental and made up.\n\nCreation of this product subjects for the act of satire, hence does not condone nor express any disparagement, insult, nor callouts whatsoever (even if some strings may found to have said so).\n\n</string>

    <!--  Install Reaction  -->
    <string name="installed_from">Installed from</string>
    <string name="install_reaction_unknown">Whoa whoa whoa, I seem couldn\u0027t observe where you installed this unlock from..</string>
    <string name="install_reaction_fdroid">F-droid? Oh yeah, but..</string>
    <string name="install_reaction_manually">You downloaded the APK directly!? But..</string>
    <string name="install_reaction_google_play">Thancc for your purchase yeay!! ... You serious right? No, I mean you could also just..</string>

    <!--  Nah who cares  -->
    <string name="nah_who_cares">Nah! Who cares?</string>
    <string name="nah_who_cares_unknown">We are still us. No change, although we are yes ran out of money so.., other ways of help is appreciated.</string>
    <string name="nah_who_cares_fdroid">It's fine.., although we are yes ran out of money so.., other ways of help is appreciated.</string>
    <string name="nah_who_cares_manually">But seriously, we are yes ran out of money so.., other ways of help is appreciated.</string>
    <string name="nah_who_cares_google_play">I mean seriously, we actually ran out of money so we'll take it (pls don\u0027t refund tho coz we mean it). And uh.. you can redownload the manually APK from our Source code and yep, it still works just so you know.. yeah.\nAlso uhh.. root cheat (set install source to market) or not uh.. I really ran out of money. Pls give me money thancc.</string>

    <!--  Stop autoclosing accounts  -->
    <string name="stop_autoclosing_accounts">Stop autoclosing accounts</string>
</resources>